Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - J
        - Jewel - Stand (disc two), 2003; SR-18233; Jewel (Box 310)
          Catalog # PR 301324; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301324 C-J
        - Jewel - Only one too (disc one), 2006; SR-18234; Jewel (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18235. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 302293; A-side Matrix # ST-A-94400-PR-302293 A1
        - Jewel - Only one too (disc two), 2006; SR-18235; Jewel (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18234. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 302293; A-side Matrix # ST-A-94400-PR-302293 C1
        - Jez Q - Voices; Psychotic, 2002; SR-18236; Jez Q (Box 310)
          Catalog # DRAMA 001; A-side Matrix # DRAMA001 A
          Dramatix
        - JG - Put down the guns, 1993; SR-18237; JG (Box 310)
          Catalog # GAS8P; A-side Matrix # GAS 11839 FDS-1
          Gasolien Alley Records
        - Jhelisa - All I need, 1993; SR-18238; Jhelisa (Box 310)
          Catalog # DOR014; A-side Matrix # DOR 014 A1
          Dorado
        - Jibri Wise One - The house the dog built, 1991; SR-18239; Jibri Wise One (Box 310)
          Catalog # 72827 38000-1; A-side Matrix # 38000-1-A
          Ear Candy
        - Jiggie - Creeping; Lovin' you, 1999; SR-18240; Jiggie; Harris, Del; Sylvia (Box 310)
          Catalog # RPROLP 4332; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-4332 A
        - Jiggie - Don't be afraid, 1998; SR-18241; Jiggie (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18242. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SPRO 30194; A-side Matrix # S-36280-RE-1
        - Jiggie - Don't be afraid, 1998; SR-18242; Jiggie (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18241. 2 copies.
        - Jill - Wait for me, 1988; SR-18243; Jill (Box 310)
          Catalog # BB103; A-side Matrix # BB-103-A
          Bush Baby Records
        - Jimmy, Bobby - Big butt, 1984; SR-18244; Jimmy, Bobby; Bobby Jimmy and The Critters (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18245. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RP-10004; A-side Matrix # RP-100004-A
          Rapsur Records
        - Jimmy, Bobby - Big butt, 1984; SR-18245; Jimmy, Bobby; Bobby Jimmy and The Critters (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18244. 2 copies.
        - Jimmy, Bobby - NY/LA rappers; Fone freak, 1988; SR-18246; Jimmy, Bobby; Bobby Jimmy and The Critters (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18247. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PVL-2-07261; A-side Matrix # PVL-2-07261-Z1
          Ruthless Records
        - Jimmy, Bobby - NY/LA rappers; Fone freak, 1988; SR-18247; Jimmy, Bobby; Bobby Jimmy and The Critters (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18246. 2 copies.
        - Jimmy, Bobby - Hip hop prankster, 1990; SR-18248; Jimmy, Bobby; Bobby Jimmy and The Critters (Box 310)
          Catalog # SL57117; A-side Matrix # 57117-A S-23110
        - Jimmy, Bobby - Rap dirty, 1990; SR-18249; Jimmy, Bobby; Bobby Jimmy and The Critters (Box 310)
          Catalog # PVL 07285; A-side Matrix # PVL-A-07285-Z1
        - Jimmy, Bobby - Ugly knuckle butt, 1985; SR-18250; Jimmy, Bobby; Bobby Jimmy and The Critters (Box 310)
          Catalog # RP 10009; A-side Matrix # RP-100009-A L-10258
        - Jimmy G And The Tackheads - The federation of tackheads, 1985; SR-18251; Jimmy G And The Tackheads (Box 310)
          Catalog # ST-12392; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12392
        - Jimmy G And The Tackheads - Lies, 1985; SR-18252; Jimmy G And The Tackheads (Box 310)
          Catalog # V-8648; A-side Matrix # V-8648 # 99798-B
        - Jimmy G And The Tackheads - Break my heart, 1985; SR-18253; Jimmy G And The Tackheads (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18254. 2 copies.
          Catalog # V-15215; A-side Matrix # V-1-15215-99803B-Z1
        - Jimmy G And The Tackheads - Break my heart, 1985; SR-18254; Jimmy G And The Tackheads (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18253. 2 copies.
        - Jimmy Z - Funky flute, 1991; SR-18255; Jimmy Z (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18256. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DMD 1708; A-side Matrix # STDM-60819-60821-60861-1
          ATCO
        - Jimmy Z - Funky flute, 1991; SR-18256; Jimmy Z (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18255. 2 copies.
        - Jin - So afraid; Señorita, 2004; SR-18257; Jin (Box 310)
          Catalog # 7087 6 18869 1 7; A-side Matrix # 07087-618869-1-7-A
        - Jinsu - One day, 2001; SR-18258; Jinsu (Box 310)
          Catalog # 822434117716; A-side Matrix # CNJ-401-A
          CNJ Records
          Rhode Island
        - Jive All-Stars - No stoppin', 1998; SR-18259; Jive All-Stars (Box 310)
          Catalog # JSDAB-42522-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-42522-1-A1
        - Jive Bunny And The Mastermixers - The album, 1989; SR-18260; Jive Bunny And The Mastermixers (Box 310)
          Catalog # FDWL 01; A-side Matrix # MFDWL 001 A
          Music Factory
        - Jive Five - Our true story, 1983; SR-18261; Jive Five (Box 310)
          Catalog # CH 76; A-side Matrix # CH 76A
        - J.J. Fad - Supersonic, 1988; SR-18262; J.J. Fad (Box 310)
          Catalog # PR 2296; A-side Matrix # STDM 54743-S4744-1
          Dream Team Records
        - J.M.B.I. - Rat in the movie's house, 1988; SR-18263; J.M.B.I. (Box 310)
          Catalog # AMR 0016; A-side Matrix # AMR 0016 A
          American Records
          Modena, Italy
        - JMC Triveni - Chutney carnival, 1996; SR-18264; JMC Triveni (Box 310)
          Catalog # JMC-1124; A-side Matrix # JMC 1124-A
          Jamaican Me Crazy Records Inc
          Richmind Hill, New York
        - Jo Jo Jr. - Let's stick together, 1993; SR-18265; Jo Jo Jr. (Box 310)
          Catalog # MRCRA 003; A-side Matrix # MRCRA-003-A
          Right Area Records
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Jobim, Tom - A arte de Tom Jobim (disc one), 1976; SR-18266; Jobim, Tom (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18267. Double album.
          Catalog # 6470 578; A-side Matrix # 6470578 A1
          Fontana
        - Jobim, Tom - A arte de Tom Jobim (disc two), 1976; SR-18267; Jobim, Tom (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18266. Double album.
          Catalog # 6470 579; A-side Matrix # 6470579 A1
        - Jocko - Rhythm talk, 1979; SR-18268; Jocko (Box 310)
          Catalog # 4Z8 3739; A-side Matrix # PIR AB-4Z8-3739-3
          Philadelphia International Records
        - Jodeci - I'm still waiting, 1992; SR-18269; Jodeci (Box 310)
          Catalog # MCA8P 2156; A-side Matrix # MCA-11309 HF-2
          Uptown Records
        - Jodeci - What about us, 1994; SR-18270; Jodeci (Box 310)
          Catalog # UPT12 54891; A-side Matrix # UPT-11979-HFA
        - Joe - Independence day; III dance music, 1999; SR-18271; Joe (Box 310)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 4562-GM001-1A
          Diamond Records
        - Joe - Independence day; III dance music, 1999; SR-18272; Joe (Box 310)
        - Joe - That girl, 2003; SR-18273; Joe (Box 311)
          Catalog # MOTR 20938-1; A-side Matrix # MOTR-20938-1A
        - Joe Cool - That's what I do at night, 1986; SR-18274; Joe Cool (Box 311)
          Catalog # WP4001; A-side Matrix # S-17157
          World Premier Records
          Decatur, Georgia
        - Joe Public - Easy come, easy go, 1994; SR-18275; Joe Public (Box 311)
          Catalog # 44 77505; A-side Matrix # XSS-77505-A
        - Joel, Billy - Tell her about it, 1983; SR-18276; Joel, Billy (Box 311)
          Catalog # AS 1738; A-side Matrix # XSS-171393 1A
        - Joel, Billy - Tell her about it, 1983; SR-18277; Joel, Billy (Box 311)
        - Joel, Billy - An innocent man, 1983; SR-18278; Joel, Billy (Box 311)
          Catalog # QC 38837; A-side Matrix # AL 38837 1R
        - Joeski Love - I know she likes Joe, 1990; SR-18279; Joeski Love (Box 311)
          Catalog # 44 73524; A-side Matrix # XSS 073524-A
        - John, Elton - Here and there, 1976; SR-18280; John, Elton (Box 311)
          Catalog # MCA-2197; A-side Matrix # MCA-992 W-12
        - John, Elton - Wrap her up, 1985; SR-18281; John, Elton (Box 311)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2374; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2374-SH1
        - John, Elton - The best of Elton John volume one, 1981; SR-18282; John, Elton (Box 311)
          Catalog # P 16196; A-side Matrix # AS 16196-2B
          Columbia Special Productions
        - Johnny Dynell and New York 88 - Jam hot, 1983; SR-18283; Johnny Dynell and New York 88 (Box 311)
          Catalog # AMC8301; A-side Matrix # AMC8301-A
          Acme Music Corporation
        - Johnny Dynell and New York 88 - The big throwdown, 1983; SR-18284; Johnny Dynell and New York 88 (Box 311)
          In same jacket as # SR-18285. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AMC 8303; A-side Matrix # AMC-8303-A-RE1
        - Johnny Dynell and New York 88 - The big throwdown, 1983; SR-18285; Johnny Dynell and New York 88 (Box 311)
          In same jacket as # SR-18284. 2 copies.
        - Johnny Hates Jazz - Heart of gold (extended version), 1988; SR-18286; Johnny Hates Jazz (Box 311)
          Catalog # VST 1045; A-side Matrix # VST 1045 A-1U-1
        - Johnny Hates Jazz - I don't want to be a hero, 1988; SR-18287; Johnny Hates Jazz (Box 311)
          Catalog # DMD 1211; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-55429-1 PRECISION
        - Johnny P - Bed time story, 1998; SR-18288; Johnny P (Box 311)
          Catalog # SPRO-13156; A-side Matrix # SPRO-7087-6-13156-1-5-A
          Rap-A-Lot Records
          Houston, Texas
        - Johnson, Al - Tranquility, 1999; SR-18289; Johnson, Al (Box 311)
          Catalog # CRC1006; A-side Matrix # CRC-1006B-A
          Clout Recording Company
        - Johnson and D - Get ready to jump, 1983; SR-18290; Johnson and D (Box 311)
          Catalog # TDE 3001; A-side Matrix # TDE-3001-A
          T.T.E.D. Records
        - Johnson, Beverly - Can't you feel it, 1979; SR-18291; Johnson, Beverly (Box 311)
          Catalog # DSC 140; A-side Matrix # DSC-140-SA
        - Johnson, J.J. - I want to know what love is, SR-18292; Johnson, J.J. (Box 311)
          Catalog # BAR 03; A-side Matrix # BAR 03-A
          Big Apple Records
        - Johnson, James Arthur - Too much is never enough, 1986; SR-18293; Johnson, James Arthur (Box 311)
          Catalog # TX-0-3005; A-side Matrix # L10770 TX-0-3005-A
          Tuxedo Music Ltd
        - Jesse Johnson's Revue - I want my girl, 1985; SR-18294; Jesse Johnson's Revue; Johnson, Jesse (Box 311)
          Catalog # SP-12144; A-side Matrix # A+M-SP-012144-A-ES1
        - Johnson, Jesse - Everybody wants somebody to love, 1988; SR-18295; Johnson, Jesse (Box 311)
          Catalog # SP-17652; A-side Matrix # A&M-AM-SP-017652-A
        - Jesse Johnson's Revue - Can you help me, 1985; SR-18296; Jesse Johnson's Revue; Johnson, Jesse (Box 311)
          In same jacket as # SR-18297. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-12129; A-side Matrix # A+M-SP-012129-A-ES1
        - Jesse Johnson's Revue - Can you help me, 1985; SR-18297; Jesse Johnson's Revue; Johnson, Jesse (Box 311)
          In same jacket as # SR-18296. 2 copies.
        - Johnson, Jesse - Every shade of love, 1988; SR-18298; Johnson, Jesse (Box 311)
          In same jacket as # SR-18299. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-5188; A-side Matrix # SPO-5188-A-ES1
        - Johnson, Jesse - Every shade of love, 1988; SR-18299; Johnson, Jesse (Box 311)
          In same jacket as # SR-18298. 2 copies.
        - Johnson, Jesse - Crazay (remix), 1986; SR-18300; Johnson, Jesse (Box 311)
          Catalog # SP-12214; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012214A-ES
        - Johnson, Jesse - She (I can't resist), 1986; SR-18301; Johnson, Jesse (Box 311)
          Catalog # SP-12219; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012219-A
        - Johnson, Jesse - Love struck, 1988; SR-18302; Johnson, Jesse (Box 311)
          Catalog # SP-12265; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012265-A-ES1
        - Justin Johnson & KMH - Dai-lo; All the hoes, 1999; SR-18303; Justin Johnson & KMH; Marz, Scotty (Box 311)
          Catalog # BLR001; A-side Matrix # BLR-001-A
          Barely Legal Records
        - Johnson, Lorraine - Feed the flame; You and me just started, 1993; SR-18304; Johnson, Lorraine (Box 311)
          Catalog # SPEC-1652; A-side Matrix # SPEC-1652-A
          Montreal, Canada
        - Johnson, Lorraine - Feed the flame; You and me just started, 1993; SR-18305; Johnson, Lorraine (Box 311)
        - Johnson, Paul - Get get down, 1999; SR-18306; Johnson, Paul (Box 311)
          Catalog # DEFECT7R; A-side Matrix # DEFECT 7RA-01-1
          Defected
        - Johnson, Smokey - It ain't my fault, 2000; SR-18307; Johnson, Smokey (Box 311)
          Catalog # NTI LP 7104; A-side Matrix # NTILP 7104-A
          NOLA Records
        - Johnson, Syleena - Hit on me (hi-tek remix), 2001; SR-18308; Johnson, Syleena; Mos Def (Box 311)
          Catalog # 9253020 P; A-side Matrix # 9253020P-A
        - Johnson, Syleena - Hit on me (hi-tek remix), 2001; SR-18309; Johnson, Syleena; Mos Def (Box 311)
          Catalog # DUTCH-37; A-side Matrix # DUTCH-37A
        - Johnson, Syleena - Hypnotic, 2005; SR-18310; Johnson, Syleena; R. Kelly; Fabolous (Box 311)
          Catalog # JDAB-68254-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-68254-1 A
        - Johnson, Troy - Trouble, 1987; SR-18311; Johnson, Troy (Box 311)
          Catalog # V-71400; A-side Matrix # V-1-71400
        - Johnsons - Jail bait, 1981; SR-18312; Johnsons; Starr, Maurice (Box 311)
          In same jacket as # SR-18313. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BIR 2009; A-side Matrix # BIR-2009-A-1-1-1
          Boston International Records
          Boston, Massachusettes
        - Johnsons - Jail bait, 1981; SR-18313; Johnsons; Starr, Maurice (Box 311)
          In same jacket as # SR-18312. 2 copies.
        - Johukames Band - De party "AIOOPS", 1986; SR-18314; Johukames Band (Box 311)
          Catalog # BSR-JB-049; A-side Matrix # BSR JB 049-A
          B's Records
        - Joi - Ghetto superstar, 1997; SR-18315; Joi (Box 311)
          Catalog # SPRO-11686; A-side Matrix # SPRO-11686-1A
          EMI Records
        - Joint Ventures - Itz da joint, 1993; SR-18316; Joint Ventures (Box 311)
          Catalog # PRO-7406; A-side Matrix # PRO-7406-A
        - Joint Ventures - Itz da joint, 1993; SR-18317; Joint Ventures (Box 311)
          Catalog # PRO-1444; A-side Matrix # PRO-1444-A
        - Joli, France - Blue eyed technology, 1983; SR-18318; Joli, France (Box 311)
          Catalog # 49-04255; A-side Matrix # XSS-169518-1A
        - Joli, France - Does he dance, 1985; SR-18319; Joli, France (Box 311)
          Catalog # 49-05191; A-side Matrix # XSS 174301 1A
        - Jonah, Julian - (There'll be a) better day, 1989; SR-18320; Jonah, Julian; Muriel, Linda (Box 311)
          Catalog # COOLX 193; A-side Matrix # COOLX 193 A1
          Cooltempo
        - Jonell - So whassup; Don't stop, 2003; SR-18321; Jonell (Box 311)
          Catalog # DEFR 15781-1; A-side Matrix # 440 063 751-1A
          Def Soul
        - Jones, Al - Whatever it takes, 1995; SR-18322; Jones, Al (Box 311)
          Catalog # 374631275-1; A-side Matrix # 374631275-1-A-G1
        - Jones, Alfonz - Champion of love, 1988; SR-18323; Jones, Alfonz (Box 311)
          Catalog # ACL 10000; A-side Matrix # ACL-100000-A
          Angel City Records
        - Jones, Alfonz - Ain't no sunshine when she's gone, 1988; SR-18324; Jones, Alfonz (Box 312)
          Catalog # ACD 500; A-side Matrix # L 30953
        - Jones, Donell - You should know; Still common, 2005; SR-18325; Jones, Donell (Box 312)
          Catalog # DONJ001; A-side Matrix # DONJ 001 A
        - Jones, Donell - Knocks me off my feet; You should know, 1996; SR-18326; Jones, Donell (Box 312)
          Catalog # 73008-24193-1; A-side Matrix # 73008-24193-1-SA
          LaFace Records
        - Jones, Donell - You know that I love you, 2002; SR-18327; Jones, Donell (Box 312)
          Catalog # 07822-15112-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-15112-1SA
          Artista
        - Jones, Donell - Better start talking, 2005; SR-18328; Jones, Donell (Box 312)
          Catalog # 82876-73474-1; A-side Matrix # LFD-70261-1 A
        - Jones, Donell - In the hood (remix), 1996; SR-18329; Jones, Donell (Box 312)
          Catalog # 73008-24172-1; A-side Matrix # 73008-24172-1-SA
        - Jones, Donell - In the hood, 1995; SR-18330; Jones, Donell (Box 312)
          Catalog # LFDP-4128; A-side Matrix # LFDP-4128-SA
        - Jones, Donell - In the hood, 1995; SR-18331; Jones, Donell (Box 312)
        - Jones, Donell - In the hood, 1995; SR-18332; Jones, Donell (Box 312)
        - Jones, Elvin - Time capsule, 1977; SR-18333; Jones, Elvin (Box 312)
          Catalog # VSD 79389; A-side Matrix # V SD 79389 A-1A
          Vanguard
        - Jones Girls - Ain't no stoppin' us now; You gonna make me love somebody else, 1979; SR-18334; Jones Girls (Box 312)
          Catalog # 4ZH 06923; A-side Matrix # 2Z8 3682-3-GIA
        - Jones, Glenn - Living in the limelight, 1987; SR-18335; Jones, Glenn (Box 312)
          Catalog # 1090-1-JDAB; A-side Matrix # 1090-1-JD-A
        - Jones, Glenn - I am somebody, 1983; SR-18336; Jones, Glenn (Box 312)
          Catalog # JD-13436; A-side Matrix # PD 13436-A-1S
        - Jones, Glenn - Finesse, 1984; SR-18337; Jones, Glenn (Box 312)
          Catalog # JW-14122; A-side Matrix # PW-14122-C
        - Jones, Glenn - Stay, 1986; SR-18338; Jones, Glenn (Box 312)
          Catalog # 5744-1-RDAC; A-side Matrix # 5744-1-RD-A-1
        - Jones, Glenn - Talk me into it, 1986; SR-18339; Jones, Glenn (Box 312)
          Catalog # JW-14328; A-side Matrix # PW-14328-A-1
        - Jones, Gloria - When I was a little girl, 1979; SR-18340; Jones, Gloria (Box 312)
          Catalog # 8522; A-side Matrix # 533-95294A
        - Jones, Gloria - Boogie oogie oogie; Bring on the love (why can't we be friends again), 1977; SR-18341; Jones, Gloria (Box 312)
          Catalog # SPRO-8822; A-side Matrix # SPRO-8822 F1
        - Jones, Grace - Hurricane, 1998; SR-18342; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          In same jacket as # SR-18343. 2 copies.
          Catalog # G828; A-side Matrix # G828A
        - Jones, Grace - Hurricane, 1998; SR-18343; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          In same jacket as # SR-18342. 2 copies.
        - Jones, Grace - Breakdown, 1980; SR-18344; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          In same jacket as # SR-18345. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-A-920; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-920-A
        - Jones, Grace - The hunter gets captured by the game, 1980; SR-18345; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          In same jacket as # SR-18344. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-A-892; A-side Matrix # PTO A 892 S A1
        - Jones, Grace - On your knees, 1979; SR-18346; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          Catalog # DISD 8869; A-side Matrix # DISD-8869-RE1-XPA-0112-S-M1
        - Jones, Grace - Slave to the rhythm, 1985; SR-18347; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          Catalog # SPRO-9533; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9533-240724-A-240710-A-Z1
          Manhattan Island Records
        - Jones, Grace - Nightclubbing, 1981; SR-18348; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          Catalog # 90093-1; A-side Matrix # STIL 835187 B
        - Jones, Grace - I'm not perfect (but I'm perfect for you), 1986; SR-18349; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          Catalog # V-56038; A-side Matrix # V156038-241146B-Z1
        - Jones, Grace - I'm not perfect (but I'm perfect for you), 1986; SR-18350; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          In same jacket as # SR-18351. 2 copies.
        - Jones, Grace - I'm not perfect (but I'm perfect for you), 1986; SR-18351; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          In same jacket as # SR-18350. 2 copies.
        - Jones, Grace - Feel up, 1981; SR-18352; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          In same jacket as # SR-18353. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRO-A-985; A-side Matrix # PRO A 985 YAA 9954 V1
        - Jones, Grace - Feel up, 1981; SR-18353; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          In same jacket as # SR-18352. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - Jones, Grace - Slave to the rhythm, 1985; SR-18354; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          Catalog # V56012; A-side Matrix # V-1-56012-240710-A-Z3
        - Jones, Grace - Slave to the rhythm, 1985; SR-18355; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          Catalog # ST-53021; A-side Matrix # ST-1-53021-Z1
        - Jones, Grace - Warm leatherette, 1980; SR-18356; Jones, Grace (Box 312)
          Catalog # 90064-1; A-side Matrix # STIL 835131 C
        - Jones, Howard - New song, 1983; SR-18357; Jones, Howard (Box 312)
          Catalog # HOW 1T; A-side Matrix # HOW 1T A
          WEA
        - Jones, Howard - New song, 1983; SR-18358; Jones, Howard (Box 312)
        - Jones, Howard - Pearl in the shell, 1984; SR-18359; Jones, Howard (Box 312)
          Catalog # ED 4992; A-side Matrix # STED-4992-A-1
        - Jones, Howard - Life in one day, 1985; SR-18360; Jones, Howard (Box 312)
          Catalog # ED 5065; A-side Matrix # STED 5065-A-3
        - Jones, Ignatius - Like a ghost, 1982; SR-18361; Jones, Ignatius (Box 312)
          Catalog # 0-29703; A-side Matrix # B-17874-SH1
        - Jones, Jill - For love, 1987; SR-18362; Jones, Jill (Box 312)
          Catalog # 0-20825; A-side Matrix # 0-20825-A-SH1
          Paisley Park Records
        - Jones, Jill - For love, 1987; SR-18363; Jones, Jill (Box 312)
        - Jones, Jill - Mia bocca, 1987; SR-18364; Jones, Jill (Box 312)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2746; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2746-SH1
        - Jones, Jimmy - Watch out for the big girl; Pick em up, SR-18365; Jones, Jimmy; Griff; Boman (Box 312)
          Catalog # CBR-205; A-side Matrix # 0104X35-A
          Club Beats Records
        - Jones, John Paul - Don't feel guilty; Wendi, 1982; SR-18366; Jones, John Paul (Box 312)
          Catalog # 001; A-side Matrix # 001A
        - Jones, Jonah - Two boys from dixieland, 1958; SR-18367; Jones, Jonah; Teagarden, Jack (Box 312)
          Catalog # ALP-303; A-side Matrix # ALP-34
          AAMCO Records
        - Jones, Karin - Under the influence of love, 1982; SR-18368; Jones, Karin (Box 312)
          Catalog # 4W9 03145; A-side Matrix # 4W9-03145AS-1A
          Handshake Records and Tapes
        - Jones, Klinte - In the heat (of the night), 1984; SR-18369; Jones, Klinte (Box 312)
          Catalog # OM 4009; A-side Matrix # OM-4009-A
          Oh My! Records
        - Jones, Klinte - In the heat (of the night), 1984; SR-18370; Jones, Klinte (Box 312)
        - Jones, Linda - Body fever (let's go party), 1981; SR-18371; Jones, Linda (Box 312)
          Catalog # SP-A-777-12; A-side Matrix # SP-A-777-12
          Spirit Records
          Memphis, Tennessee
        - Jones, London - Save our love, 1995; SR-18372; Jones, London (Box 312)
          Catalog # LSJ8P-3195; A-side Matrix # LSJ12138-B62
          Silas Records
        - Jones, London - Save our love, 1995; SR-18373; Jones, London (Box 312)
        - Jones, London - Joi, 1994; SR-18374; Jones, London (Box 312)
          Catalog # LSJ8P 3084; A-side Matrix # LSJ-12007-BG1
        - Jones, Lumishia - Give me your love; Don't waste your time, SR-18375; Jones, Lumishia; Rock-A-Bye-Fam (Box 312)
          Catalog # A-920; A-side Matrix # A 920 A
          Ray Ray Records
        - Jones, Oran "Juice" - Here I go again; 1.2.1., 1986; SR-18376; Jones, Oran "Juice" (Box 312)
          Catalog # 44 06730; A-side Matrix # XSS-175845-1A
        - Jones, Oran "Juice" - The rain, 1986; SR-18377; Jones, Oran "Juice" (Box 313)
          Catalog # CAS 2496; A-side Matrix # XSS-175398-1A
        - Jones, Oran "Juice" - The rain; Your song, 1986; SR-18378; Jones, Oran "Juice" (Box 313)
          Catalog # 44-05930; A-side Matrix # XSS-175274-1A
        - Jones, Quincy - Something I cannot have, 1999; SR-18379; Jones, Quincy; Catero (Box 313)
          In same jacket as # SR-18380. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-A-9670; A-side Matrix # PROA-9670-A-SR1
          Qwest Records
        - Unknown - I'll live 4 U, 2000; SR-18380 (Box 313)